{"data":[{"question":"Black, red, and even bright pink diamonds ________.","a":"occasionally to find","b":"occasionally found","c":"have occasionally been found","d":"have occasionally found","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Present perfect + passive voice: S + have\/has + (adv)+ been + PP.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Between the California Coast Range and the Sierra Nevada ________.","a":"great Central Valley","b":"the great Central Valley","c":"being the great Central Valley","d":"lies the great Central Valley","answer":"4","explain":"- We use the inversion with adverbial expression of place","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"It is gravity ________ objects toward the earth.","a":"pull","b":"that pulls","c":"to pull","d":"what pulls","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We use that (pronoun) as the subject in the relative clause\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"________ their territories but rather than fight, they howl.","a":"Wolves protectively jealous","b":"Jealous of wolves","c":"Protection of wolves","d":"Wolves jealously protect","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Narrative sentence: S + V + O.\u00a0\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"________ strength of 70 horses, a forklift toils all day long in a warehouse lifting great weights.","a":"Because the","b":"With the","c":"Some","d":"The","answer":"2","explain":"\n- With + Noun: to say what tool you use to do something.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"The growth of two-income families in the United States ________ of people moving to a new social class.","a":"has resulted in millions","b":"results of millions","c":"millions of results","d":"resulting in millions","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense: We often use the Present Perfect to talk about change that has happened over a period of time.\u00a0\n- Result in something: To make sth happen.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Using a globe can be ________ it is educational.","a":"enjoyable","b":"to enjoy as","c":"as enjoyable","d":"as enjoyable as","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Comparison of Equality: as + adj\/ adv+ as.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Each mediocre book we read means one less great book that we would otherwise have a chance ________.","a":"to read them","b":"read","c":"reading","d":"to read","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Have a chance to do sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Most accidents in the home can be prevented by ________ elimination of hazards.","a":"that","b":"that the","c":"there is a","d":"the","answer":"4","explain":"\n- The + Noun\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"________ problems in sailing in tropical seas is the coral reefs.","a":"One of the biggest","b":"The biggest one","c":"Of the biggest one","d":"There are the biggest","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Structure: one of + superlative preposition + plural noun.\u00a0\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"}]}